Privacy Policy

The Scranton Pocono Amateur Radio Klub (aka SPARK and herein after referred to as SPARK) and N3UVR's Backyard Weather Station (herein after referred to as the Station) are committed to protecting the privacy and accuracy of confidential information to the extent possible, subject to provisions of state and federal law. Other than as required by laws that guarantee public access to certain types of information, or in response to subpoenas or other legal instruments that authorize access, personal information is not actively shared. In particular, we do not re-distribute or sell personal information collected on our web servers.

Information Collected

We use Google Analytics and Statcounter.com to collect:

* Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used (geographic location)
* Web pages requested
* Referring web page
* Browser used
* Date and time

These websites do not associate this data with individual user identities.

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Google Analytics and Statcounter.com use cookies for session maintenance: they allow us to see which pages a given user visited, the length of time of the visit and if it is a return visit, but do not have any identifying information about the user.

Google Analytics

[How Google uses information from sites that use Google Analytics.](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)  
Google does not combine, match or cross-reference information from Google Analytics with any other user information.

Opting out

You can configure your browser to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from websites you visit. Also, [](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)[Google offers a browser extension to opt out of Google Analytics.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)[](https://help.duckduckgo.com/duckduckgo-help-pages/desktop/adding-duckduckgo-to-your-browser/)  

Email forms

This website uses email forms. Contact information from these email forms are used only to send material relating to the purpose for which it was collected and will not be sold to another party. This website will only use personal information collected from this site for the purpose of communicating with individuals who contact us via the site.

Distribution of collected information:

This website will not disclose, without your consent, personal information collected about you, except for certain explicit circumstances in which disclosure is required by law. This website will not distribute or sell personal information to third-party organizations.

Scope

This Privacy Statement applies only to SPARK and the Station.

Responsibility for External Sites

This website may contain links to other websites. Some of those websites may be operated by third parties. We provide the links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of websites operated by third parties or for your business dealings with them. Therefore, whenever you leave this website we recommend that you review each website’s privacy practices and make your own conclusions regarding the adequacy of these practices. While using this website, you may encounter hypertext links to the web pages of organizations not directly affiliated with SPARK and the Station. SPARK and the Station do not control the content or information practices of external organizations. We recommend you review the privacy statements of these organizations.

Privacy Statement Revisions

We may change this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. We encourage you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit the website. If we make a significant change to our Privacy Statement, we will post a notice on the homepage of our web site for a period of time after the change is made.  
This Privacy Statement was last revised on 18 April 2021.

How to contact us:

To contact us, use our email contact form at: [SPARK K3CSG Comment/Request Form](https://legionpost869.altervista.org/sparkemailform.html)

Return to SPARK Home Page [k3csg.org](https://k3csg.altervista.org/) or Return to Weather Station [Weather Station](https://k3csg.altervista.org/index.php)
